People say it is unfair to expect everyone to speak up against the injustices of the world.
And at one point I thought that was true.
But I know now that it is not.
I know now that the injustices of the world are committed by people who expect us to think that way.
They're the same people who told us don't share salary information so that they could be discriminatory in their salaries.
They're the same people that told us politics is personal so that we wouldn't come together as community and vote in our power.
They're the same people that tell us, you know, a woman's age is private because they want women to be shamed, to elevate, to mature, to be refined.
It is everybody's responsibility to speak up against injustice.
Not only those of us who are facing injustice, but those of us who are not.
If we are not responsible for that, then how do we expect injustice to not happen?
That is what being community is.
It is everyone working together for the betterment of everyone.
So if we don't consider it our business to speak up, then we do not consider ourselves community.
And that is exactly why they are able to do what they do to us, not just here in America, but globally.
The people who are doing injustice are speaking with actions.
The least we can do is speak with our voice.